Political Research Associates Records MS014
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Subject files, 1949 -- 2010; MS014.003; 78.0 Cubic Feet
  - House of Yahweh, 1983 -- 1997; MS014.006405; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - House Wednesday Group, 1981; MS014.006406; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - House Managers Political Action Committee, circa 1969 -- 2009; MS014.006407; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - How to Elect Christians to Public Office, Robert Simonds, 1996; MS014.006408; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Howard Center, 1998 -- 2007; MS014.006409; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Howard J. Pew, 1984; MS014.006410; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Hoy, Robert J., 1986; MS014.006411; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Hudson, George Ray, 1982; MS014.006412; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Hudson Institute, 1980 -- 1994; MS014.006413; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Hugel, Max, 1981; MS014.006414; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Hulet, Craig, 1986 -- 1992; MS014.006415; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Hull, John, 1987 -- 1991; MS014.006416; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Human Development Fund /Foundation, 1983 -- 1986; MS014.006417; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Human Development Resource Council, 1989 -- 1991; MS014.006418; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Human Events, 1989 -- 2004; MS014.006419; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Human Life Amendment, circa 1969 -- 2009; MS014.006420; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Human Life Center, 1981; MS014.006421; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Human Life Foundation, Incorporated, 1988 -- 1997; MS014.006422; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Human Life International, circa 1989 -- 1998; MS014.006423; 2 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Human Life International critics, 1990 -- 1995; MS014.006424; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Human Life Review, 1998; MS014.006425; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Human Resources Development Institute, 1986; MS014.006426; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Human Rights Documentation Exchange, 1996; MS014.006427; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Human Rights Watch, 1996 -- 1997; MS014.006428; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Humphrey, Gordon, 1983 -- 1988; MS014.006429; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Hunger Project, 1989 -- 1990; MS014.006430; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Hunt, Nelson Bunker, 1980 -- 1989; MS014.006431; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - The Hunt family, 1981; MS014.006432; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Hunt Foundation, 1984; MS014.006433; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Huntington, Samuel, 1986; MS014.006434; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Hurt, John, 1980; MS014.006435; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Hyde, Henry, circa 1980 -- 1983; MS014.006436; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Hylee, Reverend Jack, 1981; MS014.006437; 1 Folder(s) (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Icthys books, circa 1987; MS014.004701; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Identity, circa 1987 -- 2007; MS014.004702; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Identity Church, circa 1985 -- 1992; MS014.004703; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Irshin, David, circa 1984; MS014.004704; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Ignativs Press, circa 1988 -- 2005; MS014.004705; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Ikle, Fred, circa 1982 -- 1985; MS014.004706; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Illinois, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004707; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Illinois interchange, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004708; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Illinois Right to Work committee, circa 1983; MS014.004709; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Illinois South Project, circa 1987; MS014.004710; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Illinois State Legislature, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004711; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Immigration, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004712; 2 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 12-13)
  - Immigration Watch, circa 1996 -- 2001; MS014.004713; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Impressions controversy, circa 1988 -- 2001; MS014.004714; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Independence Institute, circa 1999; MS014.004715; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Independent Patriot Association, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004716; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Independent Women's Forum, circa 1995 -- 2001; MS014.004717; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Indiana, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004718; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Innis, Roy, circa 1985 -- 1992; MS014.004719; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Inside the Vatican, circa 1999; MS014.004720; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Insight, circa 1999; MS014.004721; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Insights book service, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004722; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Instauration, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004723; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Institute for American Values, circa 1998 -- 2004; MS014.004724; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Institute for Contemporary Studies, circa 1984 -- 1989; MS014.004725; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Institute for Creation Research, circa 1998 -- 1999; MS014.004726; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Institute for Creation Research / Midwest Center, circa 1999; MS014.004727; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Institute for Cultural Conservatism, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004728; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - IDEA (Institute for Democracy, Education and Assistance), circa 1986 -- 1987; MS014.004729; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Institute for Educational Affairs, circa 1987 -- 1990; MS014.004730; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Institute for First Amendment Studies, circa 1994 -- 1995; MS014.004731; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - The Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis Incorporated, circa 1991; MS014.004732; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Institute for Government and Politics, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004733; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Institute for 2000 - historical review, circa 2000 -- 2007; MS014.004734; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Institute for Historical Review, circa 1980 -- 2009; MS014.004735; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Institute for Historical Review, circa 1970 -- 1994; MS014.004736; 1 Folder(s) (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - HR video order, circa 1991; MS014.004737; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Institute for Humane Studies, circa 1999 -- 2000; MS014.004738; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Justice, circa 1996 -- 2009; MS014.004739; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Institute for Media Analysis Inc., circa 2001; MS014.004740; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, circa 2001; MS014.004741; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Pregnancy Loss, circa 1994; MS014.004742; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Regional and International Studies, circa 1985; MS014.004743; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Institute for the Secularization of Islamic Society, circa 2001; MS014.004744; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Institute for the Study of American REL Evangelicals, circa 1987 -- 1992; MS014.004745; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Western Values, circa 1987 -- 2001; MS014.004746; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Basic Life Principles, circa 1993 -- 1997; MS014.004747; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Institute for American Relations, circa 1980; MS014.004748; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Contemporary Studies, circa 1981; MS014.004749; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Institute of Cultural Affairs, circa 1986 -- 2000; MS014.004750; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Institute of Economic Democracy, circa 1983; MS014.004751; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Institute of International Education, circa 1986 -- 1988; MS014.004752; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Institute on Religion and Democracy, circa 1981 -- 2003; MS014.004753; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Institute on Religion and Democracy REL, circa 1983 -- 1990; MS014.004754; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Institute on Public Policy and Private Enterprise, circa 1984 -- 1989; MS014.004755; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Institute on Religion and Public Life, circa 1989 -- 2001; MS014.004756; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Institute on Religious Life, circa 1993 -- 1994; MS014.004757; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Institute on Terrorism and Subnational Conflicts, circa 1987 -- 1990; MS014.004758; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Intellectual Activist, The, circa 1981 -- 1982; MS014.004759; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Intelligence Digest, circa 1990; MS014.004760; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Intelligence Quotient, circa 1969 -- 1981; MS014.004761; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - InterAction/American Council Voluntary International Action, circa 1987; MS014.004762; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Inter-American Dialogue, circa 1989; MS014.004763; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Inter-American Institute of Political Science, circa 1982; MS014.004764; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Intercessors for America, circa 1984 -- 1995; MS014.004765; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Interchange Resource Center, circa 1982; MS014.004766; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Inter-Klan Newsletter and survival report, circa 1983 -- 1984; MS014.004767; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Intercollegiate Federation of Life of Pennsylvania, circa 1994; MS014.004768; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists (Intercollegiate Institute, Inc.), circa 1957 -- 1967; MS014.004769; 2 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 34-35)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, circa 1966 -- 2003; MS014.004770; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Interdenominational Foreign Mission REL Association, circa 1991; MS014.004771; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Interfaith Alliance, circa 1989 -- 2001; MS014.004772; 2 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 38-39)
  - Interfaith Coalition, circa 1994 -- 2004; MS014.004773; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Interfaith Committee Against Blasphemy, circa 1977; MS014.004774; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - International Bible Reading Association, circa 1990; MS014.004775; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - International Aid, Inc., circa 1984 -- 1988; MS014.004776; 1 Folder(s) (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - International Business Communications, circa 1986 -- 1988; MS014.004777; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - International Catholic University, circa 1995; MS014.004778; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - International Christian Aid, circa 1982; MS014.004779; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - International Christian Embassy in Jerusalem, circa 1980 -- 2001; MS014.004780; 6 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 4-9)
  - International Christian Outreach and Relief Services, INCOR, Seattle, circa 1989; MS014.004781; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - International Church of the Foursquare Gospel | Igelsia del Evangelico Cuadangular, circa 1987 -- 1989; MS014.004782; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - International Commission for Central American Recovery and Development, circa 1986 -- 1989; MS014.004783; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - International Committee for Holocaust Truth, circa 1996; MS014.004784; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - International Executive Service, circa 1985 -- 1990; MS014.004785; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - International Fellowship of Christians and Jews, circa 1995 -- 2009; MS014.004786; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - International Healing Foundation Inc., circa 1989 -- 2001; MS014.004787; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - International Gay and Lesbian Human Rights Commission, circa 1994 -- 2003; MS014.004788; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - International Health Service, circa 1987; MS014.004789; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - International historic films, circa 1983 -- 1985; MS014.004790; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - International Institute for In-Depth Evangelization, circa 1989 -- 1990; MS014.004791; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Institute of Rural Reconstruction | Movimiento Guatemlteca de Construccion Rural, circa 1987 -- 1989; MS014.004792; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - International Labor Research and Information Group, circa 1985 -- 1988; MS014.004793; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - International League for Human Rights, circa 1981 -- 1987; MS014.004794; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - International Life Services, circa 1992 -- 1993; MS014.004795; 2 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 24-25)
  - International Medical Corps, circa 1988 -- 1990; MS014.004796; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - International Rescue Committee, circa 1974 -- 1991; MS014.004797; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - International Security Council, circa 1989 -- 1990; MS014.004798; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - International Society for Individual Liberty, circa 1995 -- 2004; MS014.004799; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - InterVarsity Christian Fellowship, circa 1997; MS014.004800; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - International Voluntary Services, circa 1972 -- 1987; MS014.004801; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organizing, circa 2003 -- 2009; MS014.004802; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Invest-In-America National Council, circa 1984; MS014.004803; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Iowa, circa 1982; MS014.004804; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Iowa Freedom Foundation, circa 1989 -- 2001; MS014.004805; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Iraq, circa 1990; MS014.004806; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Iran Countra Affair, circa 1987 -- 2002; MS014.004807; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Iron Mountain, circa 1995; MS014.004808; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Report from Iron Mountain, circa 1972 -- 1996; MS014.004809; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Report from Iron Mountain final ed. Free press copies, circa 1996; MS014.004810; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Irvine, Reed, circa 1984 -- 1996; MS014.004811; 2 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 41-42)
  - Islamic extremists, circa 1993; MS014.004812; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Isaac, Rael Jean, circa 1987; MS014.004813; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - Islam - culture war, circa 1989 -- 2001; MS014.004814; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Issues and Views newsletter, circa 1990 -- 1991; MS014.004815; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Jackson, E. W., circa 1991; MS014.004816; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Jackson, Jesse, circa 1988 -- 1999; MS014.004817; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Jacobs, Charles, circa 1988; MS014.004818; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - James Madison Institute, circa 1988; MS014.004819; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Jameson Books, circa 1989 -- 2001; MS014.004820; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 51)
  - Jefferson Educational Foundation, The, circa 1990; MS014.004821; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 52)
  - Jeffries, Leonard, circa 1992; MS014.004822; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 53)
  - Jehovah's Witness, circa 1989 -- 1991; MS014.004823; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 54)
  - Jensen, Arthur, circa 1992; MS014.004824; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 55)
  - Jessup, David, circa 1981 -- 2001; MS014.004825; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 56)
  - Jesus Film Project, circa 1997 -- 2007; MS014.004826; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 57)
  - Jewish Anti-Abortion League, circa 1994; MS014.004827; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 58)
  - Jewish Defense League, circa 1984 -- 1985; MS014.004828; 1 Folder(s) (Box 45, Folder 59)
  - Jewish Right, circa 1980 -- 1994; MS014.004829; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Jews for Jesus, circa 1993 -- 2008; MS014.004830; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - John N. Olen Foundation, circa 1984; MS014.004831; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - John Randolph Club, circa 1993 -- 1994; MS014.004832; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Jones, Art, circa 1990; MS014.004833; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Bruce, circa 1985 -- 1990; MS014.004834; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Sheila, circa 1980 -- 1995; MS014.004835; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Joppa Gospel Tabernacle, Inc., circa 1980 -- 1995; MS014.004836; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Joseph McCarthy Foundation, circa 1982; MS014.004837; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Josh McDowell Ministry, circa 1999 -- 2000; MS014.004838; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Journal of Democracy, circa 1980 -- 1995; MS014.004839; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Journal of Biblical Counseling, circa 1995; MS014.004840; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Journal of Historical Review, circa 1993 -- 1998; MS014.004841; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Joyce, John T., circa 1985 -- 1990; MS014.004842; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Joyce, Michael, circa 2001; MS014.004843; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Jubilee, circa 1994 -- 1996; MS014.004844; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Judicial Watch, circa 1999 -- 2009; MS014.004845; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Justice Fellowship, circa 1999; MS014.004846; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Justice Political Action Committee, circa 1980 -- 1995; MS014.004847; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 19)
    Materials in this folder include graphic images of abortion. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
  - Just Life, circa 1990; MS014.004848; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Kach International, circa 1988; MS014.004849; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Kahane Chai, circa 1991 -- 1992; MS014.004850; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Kahane, Meir, circa 1979 -- 2004; MS014.004851; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Kahn, Herman, circa 1984; MS014.004852; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Kahn, Tom, circa 1988 -- 1989; MS014.004853; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Kampleman, Max M., circa 1984 -- 1989; MS014.004854; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Kanakha County Book Protest, circa 1974 -- 1988; MS014.004855; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Kaufman, Ron, circa 1988 -- 1990; MS014.004856; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Keating, Barbara, circa 1978; MS014.004857; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Keats, Roger, circa 1982 -- 1983; MS014.004858; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Keene, David, circa 1989; MS014.004859; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Keep the Faith Inc., circa 1980 -- 1995; MS014.004860; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Kelly, Jim, circa 1988; MS014.004861; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Kelly, Peter G., circa 1980 -- 1995; MS014.004862; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Kemble, Penn, circa 1987; MS014.004863; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Kemp, Jack, circa 1979 -- 1995; MS014.004864; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Kennedy, Anthony, circa 1988; MS014.004865; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Kennedy, Ted, circa 1933; MS014.004866; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Keyes, Alan L., circa 1988 -- 2000; MS014.004867; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Keyes, W. Augustus, circa 1981; MS014.004868; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Kimberling, Stephen, circa 1988; MS014.004869; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - King, Dr. Martin Luther, circa 1982 -- 1986; MS014.004870; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - King, Edward, circa 1982 -- 1983; MS014.004871; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - King, Rodney, circa 1993; MS014.004872; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Kingdom Computers, circa 1998; MS014.004873; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Kingdom Identify Ministries, circa 1980 -- 1995; MS014.004874; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Kirkland, Lane, circa 1988; MS014.004875; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Kirkpatrick, Jeane, circa 1977 -- 1989; MS014.004876; 2 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 48-49)
  - Kissinger, Henry, circa 1983 -- 1989; MS014.004877; 2 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 50-51)
  - Kleindienst, Richard G., circa 1981; MS014.004878; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Knauer, Virginia H., circa 1982; MS014.004879; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 53)
  - Knight Initiative, circa 1999; MS014.004880; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 54)
  - Knights of Columbus, circa 1982; MS014.004881; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 55)
  - Knights of Malta, circa 1984 -- 1991; MS014.004882; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 56)
  - Kahl - aftermath - coverup, circa 1984; MS014.004883; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 57)
  - Knowledge = Freedom, circa 1995; MS014.004884; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 58)
  - Koehl, Matt, circa 1973 -- 1977; MS014.004885; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 59)
    Materials in this folder contain racist and white supremacist language. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
  - Koehler, Rep. Judy, circa 1986; MS014.004886; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 60)
  - Kondracke, Morton, circa 1989; MS014.004887; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 61)
  - Kern, Stacy, circa 1985 -- 1991; MS014.004888; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 62)
  - Koop, Dr. C. Everett, circa 1979 -- 1988; MS014.004889; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 63)
  - Kreep, Gary C., circa 1982 -- 2007; MS014.004890; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 64)
  - Krieble Institute, circa 1996; MS014.004891; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 65)
  - Krieble, Robert, circa 1984; MS014.004892; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 66)
  - Kristol, Irving, circa 1967 -- 1986; MS014.004893; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 67)
  - Ku Klux Klan -- Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, circa 1981; MS014.004894; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 68)
  - Ku Klux Klan -- Illinois History, circa 1976; MS014.004895; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 69)
  - Ku Klux Klan -- Massachusetts, circa 1985 -- 1992; MS014.004896; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 70)
  - Ku Klux Klan, Knights of the, circa 1984 -- 1985; MS014.004897; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 71)
    Materials in this folder use racist and white supremacist language and specifically discuss recruiting children to the KKK. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
  - Ku Klux Klan, circa 1991; MS014.004898; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 72)
  - Ku Klux Klan I, circa 1983 -- 1995; MS014.004899; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 73)
    This folder contains graphic images of lynching victims. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
  - Ku Klux Klan II, circa 1979 -- 1983; MS014.004900; 1 Folder(s) (Box 46, Folder 74)
  - Peter LaBarbera, circa 1994 -- 1999; MS014.004901; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Labor for Life, circa 1985 -- 1995; MS014.004902; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Labor issues, circa 2001; MS014.004903; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - LaHaye, Beverly, circa 1995 -- 2007; MS014.004904; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - LaHaye, Tim, circa 1988 -- 2001; MS014.004905; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Laissez Faire Books, circa 1982 -- 2001; MS014.004906; 2 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 6-7)
  - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, circa 1998; MS014.004907; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Lane, Mark, circa 1979 -- 1992; MS014.004908; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Lansdale, Ed. G., circa 1984 -- 1987; MS014.004909; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Largent, Steve, circa 1999; MS014.004910; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - LaRoche, Lyndon, circa 1989 -- 1992; MS014.004911; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Law Enforcement Alliance of America, circa 2002; MS014.004912; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Lyden LaRouche, circa 1994; MS014.004913; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - LaRouche Frier, circa 1985 -- 1992; MS014.004914; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Psycho-sexual, circa 1973; MS014.004915; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - New Solidarity, New Federalist, LaRouche, circa 1986 -- 2005; MS014.004916; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Larson, Bob, circa 1999; MS014.004917; 1 Folder(s) (Box 47, Folder 18)